It's okay, no need to change shoes.
Come in.
Why hasn't my mom come back yet?
You've been doing
pretty well on that case lately.
It's my mom.
What would you like to drink?
I'll get it for you.
What's wrong?
No, it's not...
Come in, please.
It's so hard
to see you these days.
Why are you hiding?
Listen to what they're talking about.
Maybe you'll find the answer you're looking for.
You're really shuttling back and forth every day?
It's just a temporary reassignment.
It'll be over in two months.
Come on.
Have a seat.
Have you told Zhou Yang yet?
I haven't told him yet.
Then why do you come home on time every day?
What do you want to do?
Are you running for
the title of "Good Mother of China"?
No.
It's just that home is here.
I think
your Zhou Yang
is quite reliable.
With Yanyan's situation,
I can let go.
What do you have to worry about?
What's wrong?
Are you afraid Zhou Yang will learn bad habits,
or that he can't take care of himself?
No.
Actually, it's not that I don't trust Zhou Yang.
During this period,
I spend two hours every day
in the car.
When I'm spacing out, I think,
what am I doing?
Why am I exhausting myself
like this every day?
Later,
I figured it out.
You know,
I finally returned to the workplace.
If I say I'm not scared
or confused,
that would be a lie.
But,
the one
who keeps me going
is Zhou Yang.
Every day when I come home,
as long as I see him,
I feel
completely refreshed.
And the next day,
I'm ready to
keep pushing.
So,
it's not that I don't trust Zhou Yang,
it's just that
I can't live without him.
I see.
You're like an electric car,
and you need to go home to recharge every day.
Otherwise, you won't have the energy to work the next day.
Your metaphor...
Actually,
it's quite accurate.
What kind of metaphor is that?
If you put it that way,
I'm like a gasoline car.
Every day, when I'm outside,
I can fully rev up the engine.
But that's not quite right.
I should be a hybrid.
Yan is also very important to me.
So you understand me, right?
How have you been lately?
You haven't had much rest either.
As usual.
Do you have an answer?
We are still amazing
at this pace.
That's right.
You can tell
that the two kids
have completely inherited from us.
Yangyang,
why are you up so early?
Good morning, mom.
Good morning.
Don't tell me you made this.
I see how hard you work
getting up early to catch the bus every day,
so I wanted to make you breakfast.
You know everything.
So,
you won't blame me, will you?
Of course not.
I just don't want you to be too tired.
Mom, can you promise me,
that if you're too busy
or too tired,
just don't come back.
I can take care of myself.
Okay.
I promise.
Does that mean
you also promise me
I can go back and forth?
Thank you, son.
Thank you, mom.
Thank you.
You've worked hard.
It's okay.
Sit down.
Come on.
It's so beautiful.
Come on, mom.
Have a try.
It's so exquisite.
I don't want to eat it.
It's okay.
Just tell me how it is.
Okay.
Not bad.
You've got my touch.
Delicious.
Here.
Okay.
Thank you.
You should eat too.
Go ahead.
Okay.
By the way, Mom,
on the road from Yibei to Fanghe,
there's a really beautiful flower field.
Have you seen it?
I know it.
How do you know?
I even took pictures of it on my phone.
It's a secret.
Secret from me?
Next time I pass by
that sea of flowers,
I'll think of you.
Okay.
Here you are.
Thank you, Uncle Zhang.
You're welcome.
Good morning, Uncle Zhang.
Yuan,
you're up early today.
Yeah.
I'm about to
become a big brother.
I need to set a good example
for my little brother
or sister by going to bed
and waking up early.
That's impressive.
I'm heading out.
Yuan,
um,
where are your parents?
Still sleeping.
They never grow up.
You just received a big package.
I called but no one answered.
So
I just left it here.
Tell them
to come pick it up
when they're free.
Uncle Zhang, forget it.
I'll carry them back myself.
They are on vacation recently,
and get up late in the afternoon.
They take up space here.
Can you do it with your small body?
Or I'll help you.
No, no.
Your waist is not good.
You should rest more.
I play basketball.
This is a piece of cake
for me.
Well,
take it easy.
I'm leaving, Uncle Zhang.
Be careful.
Okay.
Bye.
What a big suitcase.
Qingyuan, what's wrong with your arm?
It's nothing.
Sports.
Love.
Call for
excellent photos.
Sorry.
I dropped your bag.
It's okay.
What happened to your arm?
I hurt it when I was moving stuff this morning.
The doctor said
I've got a rotator cuff strain
in my right shoulder.
But it's okay.
Then
what about the competition next Saturday?
Don't mention it.
I'm worrying about it.
Let me do it.
Just sit here.
Well,
do you want to
enter the photography contest
held by the magazine agency?
No.
Why?
Sports and Passion.
Isn't this
tailor-made for you?
The competition is more important.
I can't be distracted.
Besides, you're injured.
Let's keep things separate.
It's such a great opportunity.
If you really have no interest...
It can be folded?
I accidentally folded it.
Don't get the wrong idea.
You're all talk and no action.
You're holding the book upside down.
Mind your own hands.
Come on.
I'll do it.
Thanks.
What's this?
Don't mention it.
I hurt my right shoulder when moving things.
Doctor said to hang it a week.
Then
can you play in the next game?
Bro.
Don't you become a substitute.
I can do it.
I'll be healed in time for the game.
No problem.
Come over quickly.
I have something to tell you.
Based on the data
I've compiled,
I conclude that
we need to increase our bench depth.
Bench depth?
Indeed.
The intensity of the game
will be higher and higher.
We can't just rely on
the starting five to carry the team.
Of course, they can't do it.
So, starting from the next game,
I plan to make one of the starting players
a substitute,
also known as the sixth man.
First, rely on the four starters
to open the situation.
After the substitutes come on,
we'll use the sixth man
to change the rhythm.
That's feasible.
This person is nominally a substitute,
but in fact, he is also our
secret weapon.
And in this way,
my choice of tactics with Coach Su
can be more flexible.
But we
have to find a suitable substitute
after the starting lineup.
Are there any suitable candidates
for the substitute?
For now,
Zhu Zhan is not bad.
Is there anyone better at the perimeter?
Zhu Zhan
is better at playing inside.
I'm afraid
he can't replace Lin Qingyuan.
What are you talking about?
I don't need to be replaced.
Then, for now,
there's no suitable candidate.
Wait.
I might have
an unexpected candidate.
Hello, Su.
Chen Song, have a seat.
I've read
your script.
It's fantastic,
especially the basketball parts.
It really got me pumped.
Really?
Thank you.
What's up, Su?
Chen Song,
I've secretly looked into you.
Looked into me?
What did you find?
Your basketball game report
is so professional.
There are many
tactics in it
that I've never seen before.
Only after asking did I know
that you used to play basketball.
That's all in the past.
Tell me,
how did you play?
How long did you play?
When I was five,
I was in a youth basketball team.
My dad said
I wasn't growing tall,
so he wanted me to exercise more.
Give me the script.
Stand up.
Back up.
A bit more.
Show me how to dribble two balls.
Oh my.
So professional.
Not really.
But I did learn
from professional coaches.
Until I finished primary school,
I found I prefer
writing alone,
so I gave up.
Why didn't you tell us
such an important thing?
Is it important?
Of course.
You played basketball
for five years.
Maybe you're better
than us.
No, no, no.
I was always at the bottom of the class.
I haven't played for a long time.
It doesn't matter.
Come on.
Go to apply for joining the Basketball Club
with me now.
No, no.
I can't.
I'm afraid of holding you back.
Chen Song,
don't you want to write
better works?
The most important thing
in writing is to experience life.
Joining our basketball club
and playing more games
will surely inspire you.
Actually, I can learn by watching you.
It's the same.
It's not the same.
I've read scripts,
but does that mean I can write?
Think about it.
This is a big opportunity.
If you miss it,
you might never get another.
Fine.
If you really don't want to
play with us,
then forget it.
Let's just pretend
we never met.
You're still my good junior.
I'll still look out for you.
I'm not sad at all.
See you.
Su.
How about I give it a try?
That's what I'm waiting for.
Come on.
Catch the ball.
Nice!
Not bad, Chen Xiaosong.
You're much better than I thought.
Your basic skills are solid.
It's clear you've
had professional training.
Really,
I still have a long way to go.
I need to find my groove.
Seniors,
what do you think?
Okay.
I agree.
But you're from the junior high department.
Coach Su and I
will apply to Mr. Wang
to let you join the club.
Wait.
I have no objection to Chen Song joining the club.
But
he won't take my place as a starter, will he?
We'll discuss this later.
You should focus on recovering.
Don't worry about these.
No.
I have to make my attitude clear to you.
This game
is very important to me.
I can't be on the bench.
Because after watching
this game,
your parents will go on a road trip.
Yeah.
They won't be able to watch
the rest of the games.
It's like a child's play.
According to Fu Binyan's analysis,
Xu Anbo is the one
with the most unstable condition.
Can't he be the sixth man?
I'm fine with it.
It's indeed rare to have a center
as the sixth man.
But in our case,
it's not gonna make much difference.
Anyway, my injury doesn't matter.
What are you doing?
I'll prove it to you.
Lin Qingyuan,
be careful.
are you done?
I'm not.
I was
forced to do it today,
but
I'm sure I'll be fine
during the competition.
Besides,
you played with a wrist injury
before, didn't you?
I can objectively assess
my own injury.
Can you?
You just want to show off.
Why do you say that?
Gu Chenyang,
after all this time,
you still look down on me.
Say something.
Do you think
Gu Chenyang is right?
I'll do whatever the team decides.
I'll do whatever the team needs,
whether it's as a sub or a starter.
But please stop arguing.
I...
Me too.
Alright,
let's not be so tense.
We've got a new teammate here.
Cheer up.
I'll prove to you all
that I'm reliable.
Lin Qingyuan!
Where are you going?
Keep practicing.
Take a break and recover these days.
Don't let it get to you.
This guy is impressive!
Even with a hand injury,
he's still giving it his all.
Lin Qingyuan!
Hello, principal.
Remember to balance study and rest.
Do your best in the competition.
I'm looking forward to your good results.
Thank you, principal.
Come on.
Cheer up!
Thank you.
He's been so cold to me these days.
He's still mad at me.
I told him to rest and recover,
but he's training even harder.
I saw it too.
At this rate,
he'll end up injuring himself.
Bah, bah, bah.
But why has he been
eating chicken wingtips lately?
Does he think
wingtips can help
build up his shoulders?
Definitely.
Why is he
so angry this time?
It doesn't make sense.
It's all because of you.
Why?
You bunch of idiots.
You.
Come with me.
I'll go first.
Okay, bye.
What's going on?